The Mentorians are a warrior race. For centuries they have been conquering the Northern Galaxies but 300 years ago when our people first met we knew that war would be inevitable. At first the war was in their favour but after the humans made their alliance with the Antolics things changed. Losses turned into victories and we started to gain back systems, but soon it devolved into a stalemate. For more than 130 years now we have been playing a back and forth game with no end in sight. At least, until recently when a new weapon was discovered that has the potential to change everything.
